Guide to the Miner Searle Bates Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Correspondence, Series I
  - General Correspondence
    - Thomson, James C., 1961-1968 (Box 10, Folder 176)
    - U (Box 10, Folder 177)
    - Union Theological Seminary (see also: Bennett, John C. Missionary Research Library Van Dusen, Henry P. Handy, Robert Jackson, Herbert C.), 1950 (Box 10, Folder 178)
    - United Board for Christian Colleges in China (see also: China era corres.), 1951 (Box 10, Folder 179)
    - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia (see also: Fenn, William P.), 1965-1978, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 179)
    - United Christian Missionary Society (see: Christian Church - Disciples of Christ)
    - V (Box 10, Folder 180)
    - Van Dusen, Henry P. (see also: China era corres.), 1952-1963 (Box 10, Folder 181)
    - Wa - Wen (Box 10, Folder 182)
    - Wes (Box 10, Folder 183)
    - Wh - Wia (Box 10, Folder 184)
    - Wic - Wil (Box 10, Folder 185)
    - Wo - Wu (Box 10, Folder 186)
    - World Council of Churches, 1954-1965, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 187)
    - Y (Box 10, Folder 188)
    - Yale Divinity School Library (see aIso: American Theological Library Association, China Records Project), 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 189)
    - Zia, N. Z., 1952-1977, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 190)
    - Christian names and anonymous (Box 10, Folder 191)
    - Fragments (Box 10, Folder 192)
- China Notes and Sources, Series II
  The notes and sources of Series II are organized in eight categories:
  A. Material arranged by outline number (according to outline devised by Bates).
  B. Material arranged by author or editor of source monographs, essays and theses. A select list of titles follows the list of authors and editors in this register; a complete list of titles is available in the first folder of this section.
  C. Periodical articles, arranged by author.
  D. Notes, photocopies, and summaries from periodicals, arranged alphabetically by title of the periodical and chronologically within each title.
  E. Miscellaneous notes and references on 3" x 5" cards or sheets of paper.
  F. Miscellaneous notes and references on 5 1/2" x 8 1/2" sheets of paper.
  G. Mixed format notes and sources related to: organizations, conferences, topics.
  H. Chinese language sources.
  - A. By Outline Number
    - I. 1890-1906
      - 1. Society and State: General (Box 11, Folder 193)
      - 1. Society and State: Education (Box 11, Folder 194)
      - 1. Society and State: Footbinding, polygamy, infanticide (Box 11, Folder 195)
      - 1. Society and State: Opium (Box 11, Folder 196)
      - 2. Government and legal relations (Box 11, Folder 197-198)
      - 3. Clashing of cultures: General (Box 11, Folder 199-201)
      - 2. and 3. (folder labeled "Treaties") (Box 11, Folder 202)
      - 3., 4., and 5. (Anti-missionary violence) (Box 12, Folder 203)
      - 4. Reform and reformers - crisis of imperialist encroachment: (folder labeled "Encroachment") (Box 12, Folder 204)
      - 4. Reform and reformers - crisis of imperialist encroachment: Boxer crisis (Box 12, Folder 205-210)
      - 4. Reform and reformers - crisis of imperialist encroachment: General (Box 12, Folder 211-212)
      - 1. Broad introductory overview (Box 13, Folder 213)
      - 2., 3. Missions and churches (Box 13, Folder 214)
      - 4. Major aims, policies, adaptation (Box 13, Folder 215)
      - 5. Christian thought: concern with Chinese religions (Box 13, Folder 216-217)
      - 6. Methods and programs (special groups) (Box 13, Folder 218)
      - 7. Evangelization, growth (Box 13, Folder 219)
      - 8. Religious education, training of workers (Box 13, Folder 220)
      - 9. Education: schools and colleges (Box 13, Folder 221)
      - 10. Service: medical, social, YMCA and YWCA: General including famine relief (Box 13, Folder 222)
      - 10. Service: medical, social, YMCA and YWCA: Medical (Box 13, Folder 223-224)
      - 11. Bible, Christian literature (Box 14, Folder 225-227)
      - 12. The Chinese Christian community (Box 14, Folder 228)
      - 13. Missionaries: select aspects of life (Box 14, Folder 229)
      - General (Box 14, Folder 230)
    - II. 1907-1922
      - 1. Society, government, law (Box 14, Folder 231)
      - 2. Currents of thought, education (Box 14, Folder 232)
      - 3. Religion (Box 14, Folder 233)
      - 1. Broad view, cooperation, union (Box 14, Folder 234)
      - 2. The churches and their selfhood (Box 14, Folder 235)
      - 3. Missions as working bodies (Box 15, Folder 236)
      - 4. Aims, policies, adaptation, socio-ethical concerns (Box 15, Folder 237)
      - 5. Theology and Christian thought (Box 15, Folder 238)
      - 6. Programs, methods, special groups (Box 15, Folder 239)
      - 7. Evangelism and revivals (Box 15, Folder 240)
      - 8. Religious education and training of workers (Box 15, Folder 241)
      - 9. Education: Christian schools, colleges, universities (Box 15, Folder 242)
      - 10. Service: Medical (Box 15, Folder 244)
      - 10. Service: China Medical Board, PUMC, Rockefeller Foundation (Box 15, Folder 245)
      - 10. Service: Nursing (Box 15, Folder 246)
      - 10. Service: Social Services (Box 15, Folder 247)
      - 10. Service: YMCA and YWCA (Box 15, Folder 248)
      - 11. Christian literature and Bible (Box 15, Folder 249)
      - 12. Chinese Christian community (Box 15, Folder 250)
      - 13. External relations; missionaries, home base (Box 15, Folder 251)
    - III. 1922-1937
      - 1. Society, government, law (Box 16, Folder 252-253)
      - 2. Currents of thought, education (Box 16, Folder 254)
      - 3. Religions (Box 16, Folder 255)
      - 1. Broad view, cooperation, union (Box 16, Folder 256)
      - 2. Churches, their development, self-reliance (Box 16, Folder 257)
      - 3. Missions as working bodies (Box 16, Folder 258)
      - 4. Aims, policies, communication, adaptation (Box 16, Folder 259)
      - 5. Theology and Christian thought, Chinese religions (Box 16, Folder 260)
      - 6. Programs, methods, special groups (Box 16, Folder 261)
      - 7. Evangelism and revivals (Box 16, Folder 262)
      - 8. Religious education, Sunday Schools, training of workers (Box 16, Folder 263)
      - 9. Education: General (Box 17, Folder 264)
      - 9. Education: Primary, normal, kindergarten (Box 17, Folder 265)
      - 9. Education: Middle Schools (Box 17, Folder 266)
      - 9. Education: Colleges (Box 17, Folder 267)
      - 9. Education: Government relationships (Box 17, Folder 268)
      - 9. Education: General governement education (Box 17, Folder 269)
      - 9. Education: Adult, special, vocational (Box 17, Folder 270)
      - 9. Education: Women and girls (Box 17, Folder 271)
      - 9. Education: Associations (Box 17, Folder 272)
      - 10. Service: Medical (Box 17, Folder 273-274)
      - 10. Service: China Medical Board, PUMC, Rockefeller Foundation (Box 17, Folder 275)
      - 10. Service: Nursing (Box 17, Folder 276)
      - 10. Service: Rural Work (Box 17, Folder 277)
      - 10. Service: Rural work - Megginson thesis (Box 18, Folder 278)
      - 10. Service: Rural work - Price book (Box 18, Folder 279)
      - 10. Service: YMCA, student work (Box 18, Folder 280)
      - 10. Service: YWCA (Box 18, Folder 281)
      - 11. Christian literature and Bible (Box 18, Folder 282)
      - 12. Chinese Christian community (Box 18, Folder 283)
      - 13. External relations; missionaries, home base (Box 18, Folder 284)
      - 14. Roman Catholic missions (Box 18, Folder 285)
    - IV. 1937-1950
      - 2. Churches, their development, self-reliance (Box 18, Folder 286)
      - 10. Service; medical, social, rural, YMCA, YWCA (Box 18, Folder 287)
  - B. By Author or Editor of Source
    - Abend, Ady, Allan: Incl. Ady, M. S., "The South China Mission (Presbyterian U.S.A.), An Inquiry", 1940 (Box 19, Folder 288)
    - Anderson, M. R. (Box 19, Folder 289)
    - Anderson, R. K., "Venture of Faith: The Story of the Canadian Mission in Manchuria" (Box 19, Folder 290)
    - Armerding, Athenoux, Ayers: Incl. Armerding, Hudson T., "The China Inland Mission and Some Aspects of Its Work; Pre-1948" (Ph.D. Thesis) (Box 19, Folder 291)
    - Bacon, Baller, Balme (Box 19, Folder 292)
    - Band (Box 19, Folder 293)
    - Barber, Barbour, Barnett: Incl.Barnett, Eugene E., "As I Look Back", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 294)
    - Bau, Beach, Beaton: Incl. Bau, Mingchien J.,"The Foreign Relations of China: A History and a Survey" and Beaton, Kenneth J.," West of the Gorges", 1921, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 295)
    - Beaver, Beck, Belpaire: Incl. Beck, Karl H., "Communist Impact on the Church", n.d. (Box 19, Folder 296)
    - Bentley, Bitton, Blakeslee (Box 19, Folder 297)
    - Bliss, Bodde: Incl. typescript biography of Dr. Edward Bliss and Bodde, Derk, "The New Ideology in the Old China", n.d., 1951 (Box 19, Folder 298)
    - Bohr (Box 19, Folder 299)
    - Boorman, Borst-Smith, Boyd: Incl. Boorman, Howard L., "China: Yesterday and Tomorrow " and Boyd, H. A., "Conflicting Claims in China", 1968, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 300)
    - Boynton, Charles L., "Protestant Missionaries to China" (Lists), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 301)
    - Bradshaw, Breslin, Brewster: Incl. Bradshaw, N. E. Eloise, "China Log" (Memoir) and Breslin, Thomas A., "Corporatist Vision and Liberal Tactics: The American Catholic Missionaries in China, 1918-1941" (Box 20, Folder 302)
    - Brooks, Rachel, "The YMCA Government of China", n.d. (Box 20, Folder 303)
    - Broomhall (Box 20, Folder 304)
    - Broughton, Brown, A. J., Brown, F. (Box 20, Folder 305)
    - Brown, Margaret H., "History of the Honan (North China) Mission of the United Church of Canada", n.d. (Box 20, Folder 306)
    - Brown, Margaret H., "MacGillivary of Shanghai", 1968 (Box 20, Folder 306)
    - Bruce, Buck, J. L.: Incl. Buck, John L., "Some Basic Agricultural Problems of China", 1947 (Box 20, Folder 307)
    - Buck, P. Burgess, Burkholder: Incl. Burkholder, Lawrence J., "Rethinking Christian Life and Mission in Light of the Chinese Experience", 1977 (Box 20, Folder 308)
    - Burton (Box 20, Folder 309)
    - Cadbury, Capen (Box 20, Folder 310)
    - Lutz (Box 20, Folder 311)
    - Carlberg (Box 20, Folder 312)
    - Carson (Box 20, Folder 313)
    - Casselman, Arthur V., "It Happened in Hunan: A Narrative of a China Mission", 1951 (Box 21, Folder 314)
    - Caterer, Chamberlin, Chan, W.: Incl. Chamberlin, Wilbur J., "Ordered to China", 1903 (Box 21, Folder 315)
    - Chan, F. Gilbert, "Liao Chung-K'ai and the Labor Movement in Kwangtung, 1924-1925", 1975 (Box 21, Folder 316)
    - Chandler, Robert E., "Sketch of Chang Heng-Ch'iu of the North China Kung Li Hui" (Box 21, Folder 316)
    - Chang: Incl. Chang, Fu Siang," Rural Reconstruction in Under-Developed Areas and the Contributions of the Christian Movement" (Thesis) (Box 21, Folder 317)
    - Chao, Jonathan, "Christian Community Life in a Chinese Village, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 318)
    - Chao, Jonathan Some Ideas on the Direction of Chinese Theological Development", n.d. (Box 21, Folder 318)
    - Chapman, H. Owen, "The Second Reformation", 1968 (Box 21, Folder 318)
    - Chen, Chi-yun, "Liang Chi'-Ch'ao's 'Missionary Education': A Case Study of Missionary Influence on the Reformers", n.d. (Box 21, Folder 318)
    - Chen, Ellen Marie, "The Unitive Way - Taoism - Ch'an and Christianity", 1977 (Box 21, Folder 319)
    - Chen, Theodore H. E., "People's Republic of China", 1949-1967 1968 (Box 21, Folder 319)
    - Cheng, C. Y.," Some Problems: Confronting the Christian Movement in China", 1927 (Box 21, Folder 319)
    - Chesnaux, Chiang, M., Chiang, K. (Box 21, Folder 320)
    - Ching, Christy: Incl: Ching, Julia, "The Problem of God in Confucianism", n.d. (Box 21, Folder 321)
    - Chu, Finley M., "China's Old Culture and New Order" (Ph.D. Thesis), 1955 (Box 21, Folder 322,323)
    - Chu (Box 21, Folder 324)
    - Clark, Close, Clubb (Box 21, Folder 325)
    - Cohen, Condit, Cooper: Incl. Cooper, Luther G.,"Confucianism in Modern China" (S.T.M. Thesis), 1937 (Box 21, Folder 326)
    - Copland (Box 22, Folder 327)
    - Corbett, C. H., Cordier (Box 22, Folder 329)
    - Cormack, J. G., "The Early Days of Western Medicine in Peking", 1924 (Box 22, Folder 330)
    - Cornaby, Costantini, Couturier (Box 22, Folder 331)
    - Craighill, Cressy, E. H., Cressy (Box 22, Folder 332)
    - Croizier, Crouch, Curti: Incl. Crouch, Archie R., "The Church in Taiwan: A Declaration of Self-Determination", n.d. (Box 22, Folder 333)
    - Dachlin, I., Davis, DeBary: Incl. DeBary, William T., "Spiritual Cultivation and Intellectual Enlightenment in Neo-Confucian Thought" (Box 22, Folder 334)
    - DeFrancis, DeGroot, DeGruche (Box 22, Folder 335)
    - DeKorne, DeMailla (Box 23, Folder 336)
    - Deming (Box 23, Folder 337)
    - Dennis, Desmit, Dewey (Box 23, Folder 338)
    - Dieux, Dirlik, Dufay (Box 23, Folder 339)
    - Eastman, Eberhard, Edwards, E. H. (Box 23, Folder 340)
    - Edwards, D. W. (Box 23, Folder 341)
    - Faber: Incl. Faber, Knud, "Report on Medical Schools in China", 1931 (Box 23, Folder 342)
    - Fairbank, Jonn K., "The Many Faces of Protestant Missions in China and the United States" (Box 23, Folder 343)
    - Fairbank, Fearn, Fehl: Incl. Fairbank, Wilma, "Report from the Cultural Attache", n.d. (Box 23, Folder 344)
    - Fenn, Ferguson (Box 23, Folder 345)
    - Fisher, A. J. (Box 23, Folder 346)
    - Fisher, G. M. (Box 23, Folder 347)
    - Fitch (Box 24, Folder 348)
    - Ford, E. L., Ford, H., Forsythe (Box 24, Folder 349)
    - Fosdick, Foster, French (Box 24, Folder 350)
    - Fried, Frillman: Incl. Fried, Morton H., "Anthropology and Sociology in China", 1958 (Box 24, Folder 351)
    - Fulton, Fung (Box 24, Folder 352)
    - Gamble (Box 24, Folder 353)
    - Garrett, Garside (Box 24, Folder 354)
    - Geng, George Yuen-Hsioh, "The Promotion of the Economic Welfare of the Chinese People through the Protestant Churches in China" (Ph.D. Thesis), 1951 (Box 24, Folder 355)
    - Gibson, Giedt, Gleason: Incl. Giedt, E. H., "What Did Communism and the Communist State Bring to the Chinese Christian Community as Opportunities and Challenges, Fundamental Issues and Beliefs, Concrete Problems and Demands?", ca. 1956 (Box 25, Folder 356)
    - Glover, Glover-Kane, Goforth (Box 25, Folder 357)
    - Goldman, Goodrich: Incl. Goldman, Merle, "China's Anti-Confucian Campaign", 1973-1974 n.d. (Box 25, Folder 358)
    - Goodsell (Box 25, Folder 359)
    - Goyan, Grabhill (Box 25, Folder 360)
    - Gregg, Gross-Aschhoff (Box 25, Folder 361)
    - Haglund, Hallencrentz, Han: Incl. Han, Yu Shan, "Christian Worship in China", 1926 (Box 25, Folder 362)
    - Harris, Hart, Hay: Incl. Harris, Willie P., "History of Nursing in China" (M.A. Thesis), 1953 (Box 25, Folder 363)
    - Hayward, Hedley, Heeren (Box 25, Folder 364)
    - Hewlett, Hinckley (Box 25, Folder 365)
    - Hipps (Box 25, Folder 366)
    - Ho and Tang (Box 25, Folder 367)
    - Hoang, Hockin, Hodous (Box 26, Folder 368)
    - Hoh, Holden (Box 26, Folder 369)
    - Houghton, Hsiao, Hsu, E., Hsu, P. C. (Box 26, Folder 370)
    - Hu, C.T., Hu, S., Hudspeth (Box 26, Folder 371)
    - Hughes (Box 26, Folder 372)
    - Hume, Edward H., "Christian Medical Work and the Chinese Government", 1937 (Box 26, Folder 373)
    - Hunter, Huntington, Husemann (Box 26, Folder 374)
    - Hyatt, Irwin, "Lessons of Missionary Experience: The Lottie Moon Story", 1972 (Box 26, Folder 375)
    - Iisaka, Yoshiaki, "Japanese Christians Look at China Problem", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 376)
    - Israel, John, "Southwest Associated University: Survival as an Ultimate Value", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 376)
    - Jen (Box 26, Folder 377)
    - Jenkins (Box 26, Folder 378)
    - Johnson, E. H., Johnson, Rita, Johnston: Incl. Johnson, Rita, "Continuity and Change: Mission Attitudes Toward China", 1972 (Box 27, Folder 379)
    - Jolliffee, Jomin, Jones: Incl. Jones, F. C., "Manchuria in 1945-1946", 1947 (Box 27, Folder 380)
    - Kane, J. Herbert (Box 27, Folder 381)
    - Kane, J. Herbert, Kernahan, Keyte (Box 27, Folder 382)
    - Kiao-ou Ki-Lio (Box 27, Folder 383)
    - Kiang Wen Han, "Chinese Students and Religion - A Symposium", 1936 (Box 27, Folder 384)
    - Kiang Wen Han, "The Student Situation in China", 1932 (Box 27, Folder 384)
    - Kiang Wen Han, "Christianity and Marx-Leninism", 1950 (Box 27, Folder 384)
    - Kilborn, O. L., Kilborn, Leslie G., "Our Last Term in China: 1949-1952" (Box 27, Folder 384)
    - Kinnear, Koo, Krang (Box 27, Folder 385)
    - Ku, H. M., Ku, T. J., Kuhn: Incl. Ku, Tun-Jou, "Notes on the Chinese Version of the Bible", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 386)
    - Lacy, W. N., Lacy, Creighton, "Christian Missions Confront Communism, 1921-1948", ca. 1955 (Box 27, Folder 387)
    - Lamberton (Box 27, Folder 388)
    - Lamson, Lane, Lang (Box 27, Folder 389)
    - Lary, Lathan (Box 27, Folder 390)
    - Latourette, Kenneth S., "The History of Early Relations Between the United States and China, 1784-1844" (Ph.D. Thesis) (Box 27, Folder 390)
    - Lattimore, Lautenschlager (Box 27, Folder 391)
    - Lefeuvre (Box 27, Folder 392)
    - Lesourd, Levenson (Box 28, Folder 393)
    - Leung, S. C., "An Evaluation of the Christian Universities in China", 1958 (Box 28, Folder 393)
    - Lewis, Charlton M., "The Opening of Hunan" (Ph.D. Thesis), 1965 (Box 28, Folder 394)
    - Leyssen, Li (Box 28, Folder 394)
    - Liang (Box 28, Folder 395)
    - Lin, Ching-Jin, "Report of Work at Fukien Christian University, 1934-1935" (Box 28, Folder 396)
    - Little (Box 28, Folder 396)
    - Lutz, Jessie G., "China's Response to Western Education: The Role of the Christian Colleges", ca. 1968 (Box 28, Folder 397)
    - Lyall, Lyon (Box 28, Folder 398)
    - McDonald (Box 28, Folder 399)
    - MacGillivary, D., "A Century of Protestant Missions in China, 1807-1907" (Box 28, Folder 400, 401)
    - MacInnis, Donald, "The China Struggle and Christian Missions", 1967 (Box 29, Folder 402)
    - McIntosh (Box 29, Folder 402)
    - Maclagan (Box 29, Folder 403)
    - MacNair, H. F., "Critical Moments in the History of Christianity in China", 1925 (Box 29, Folder 404)
    - Martin, Masland, Masson: Incl. Masland, John W., "Communism and Christianity in China", 1951 (Box 29, Folder 405)
    - Matthews, B. ;Matthews, Harold S., "Lessons To Be Learned from the Experiences of Christian Missions in China (NCCC)", 1951 (Box 29, Folder 406)
    - Megginson, William J.,"The Rural Work of American Protestant Missionaries in China, 1911-1937" (B.A. Thesis and Bates' notes) (Box 29, Folder 407, 408)
    - Melby (Box 29, Folder 409)
    - Merwin, Wallace C., "Adventure in Unity; The Church of Christ in China ", ca. 1972 (Box 29, Folder 410-411)
    - Merwin, Wallace C., "Adventure in Unity; The Church of Christ in China " (Box 30, Folder 412)
    - Meskill, Miao, Miao and Price: Incl. Miao, Chester, "How Did the American Imperialists Destroy the Three-Self Reform Movement through National Christian Council", 1951 (Box 30, Folder 413)
    - Michie, Millard, Miller (Box 30, Folder 414)
    - Mills, Milne, Moffett: Incl. Moffett, Anna E. The Nanking Tragedy - A Personal Statement, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 415)
    - Monsen, Monsterleet, Moreau and Masson (Box 30, Folder 416)
    - Morse, H. B., Morse and MacNair, Morton (Box 30, Folder 417)
    - Munro (Box 30, Folder 418)
    - Nahn, Nairne, Najarian (Box 30, Folder 419)
    - Norris, Noyes (Box 30, Folder 420)
    - Ogilvie, O'Neill, Oosthuicen, Oosthuizen (Box 30, Folder 421)
    - Park, Patterson (Box 30, Folder 422)
    - Pelissier, Perry: Incl. Perry, Elizabeth J., "Peasant Violence in Huai-Pei: An Ecological Approach to Rebellion and Revolution", 1978 (Box 30, Folder 424)
    - Pillai, Joachim, "Maoist Ethics and Judaeo-Christian Traditions", 1974 (Box 30, Folder 424)
    - Piolet, Planchet, Porter (Box 31, Folder 425)
    - Poteat, Powell (Box 31, Folder 426)
    - Pratt, J. B., Pratt, J. T. (Box 31, Folder 427)
    - Price, Frank W., "The Church in China Today", n.d. (Box 31, Folder 428)
    - Price, Frank W. History of Nanking Theological Seminary, 1911-1961 (Box 31, Folder 428)
    - Purcell, Pye (Box 31, Folder 429)
    - Quigley (Box 31, Folder 430)
    - Rabe, Valentin H. The American Protestant Foreign Missionary Movement, 1880-1920 (Ph.D. Thesis), 1964 (Box 31, Folder 431)
    - Rattenbury, Rawlinson (Box 31, Folder 431)
    - Read, Katherine L., "Bernard Emms Read: Scientist - World Traveler Humanitarian; An Account of One Life in China, 1909-1949", n.d. (Box 31, Folder 432)
    - Rees, Reid (Box 31, Folder 432)
    - Reinsch, Reisner, Reynolds (Box 31, Folder 433)
    - Richard, Richardson, Richter (Box 31, Folder 434)
    - Robertson, Robson, Ross (Box 31, Folder 435)
    - Rowlands, Rowley (Box 31, Folder 436)
    - Rubinstein, Murray A., "Perishing Heathens and Parochial Preachers: 19th Century American Missionary Perceptions of the Chinese Religious Tradition" (Box 31, Folder 436)
    - Sailer, Randolph C. Robert B. Fulton, "Suggestions for Working to Understand China and America Better", 1977 (Box 31, Folder 437)
    - Sallee, Schlunk (Box 31, Folder 437)
    - Scheider, Shrecker (Box 32, Folder 438)
    - Schulman, Irwin J., "The Emergence of the Boxers ", 1974 (Box 32, Folder 438)
    - Schultheis (Box 32, Folder 439)
    - Schwarcz, Vera, "May Fourth as Allegory: Intellectuals and the Historiography of Remembrance", 1978 (Box 32, Folder 439)
    - Schwartz (Box 32, Folder 439)
    - Scott, Selden, Semedo (Box 32, Folder 440)
    - Shao and Palmer, Sih, Simpson (Box 32, Folder 441)
    - Smith, J. M. (Box 32, Folder 442)
    - Smith, S. P. (Box 32, Folder 443)
    - Smith, W.E. (Box 32, Folder 444)
    - Skinner, Smythe (Box 32, Folder 445)
    - Smythe, Lewis S. C., "Changes in the Christian Message for China by Protestant Missionaries", 1928 (Box 32, Folder 446)
    - Solomon, Song, Soothill (Box 32, Folder 447)
    - Sovik, A., "Church and State in Republican China" (Ph.D. Thesis), 1952 (Box 32, Folder 448)
    - Sovik, E. (Box 32, Folder 449)
    - Speer (Box 32, Folder 450)
    - Spence, Stuart (Box 32, Folder 451)
    - Studley, Ellen M., "Winning Chinese Youth to Christ" (B.D. Thesis), 1956 (Box 33, Folder 452)
    - Suekane, Swenson (Box 33, Folder 453)
    - Sydenstricker, Absalom, "Our Life and Work in China", 1923 (Box 33, Folder 453)
    - Syrdal, Rolf A., "American Lutheran Mission in China" (Ph.D. Thesis), 1942 (Box 33, Folder 454)
    - T'ang, C., T'ang, L., Tatchell (Box 33, Folder 455)
    - Tatford, Tatlow, Taylor, H. B. (Box 33, Folder 456)
    - Taylor, Mrs. H. (Box 33, Folder 457)
    - Taylor, Joseph, "West of the Yang-tze Gorges", 1936 (Box 33, Folder 458)
    - Tcheng, Teele (Box 33, Folder 459)
    - Teng, S. Y., "Christian Assumptions in Occidental Histories of China", 1951 (Box 33, Folder 459)
    - Teng and Fairbank, Thompson, L. G. (Box 33, Folder 460)
    - Thompson, P., Thompson, R. W. (Box 33, Folder 461)
    - Thomson, J. C. (Box 34, Folder 462)
    - Thomson, J. O., "Cycle of Cathay", n.d. (Box 34, Folder 462)
    - Thornbery (Box 34, Folder 462)
    - Tsang (Box 34, Folder 463)
    - Tsu, Tyau (Box 34, Folder 464)
    - Van Dusen, Van Oost (Box 34, Folder 465)
    - Varg, Paul A., "Missionaries and China's Nationalistic Revolution", 1971 (Box 34, Folder 466)
    - Vincent (Box 34, Folder 467)
    - Virginia Therese, "Timothy Richard's Theory of Christian Missions to the Non-Christian World" (Thesis), 1966 (Box 34, Folder 467)
    - Vogel, Ezra F., "The Unlikely Hero: The Social Role of the May 4th Writers", n.d. (Box 34, Folder 467)
    - Vohra (Box 34, Folder 468)
    - Wakefield, Walker, Wallace, L. E. (Box 34, Folder 469)
    - Wallace, E. W., Walmesley (Box 34, Folder 470)
    - Walmesley, L. C. (Box 34, Folder 471)
    - Walter, Wang, C. H., Wang, M. T. (Box 34, Folder 472)
    - Wang, Warneck, Warren (Box 34, Folder 473)
    - Weber, H. R., Weber, M. (Box 34, Folder 474)